const questions = [
  {
    question: "to meet, to see",
    answer: "au",
    display: "あう",
  },
  {
    question: "to play",
    answer: "asobu",
    display: "あそぶ",
  },
  {
    question: "to wash",
    answer: "arau",
    display: "あらう",
  },
  {
    question: "to be (object)",
    answer: "aru",
    display: "ある",
  },
  {
    question: "to say",
    answer: "iu",
    display: "いう",
  },
  {
    question: "to go",
    answer: "iku",
    display: "いく",
  },
  {
    question: "to be (living beings)",
    answer: "iru",
    display: "いる",
  },
  {
    question: "to sing",
    answer: "utau",
    display: "うたう",
  },
  {
    question: "to sell",
    answer: "uru",
    display: "うる",
  },
  {
    question: "to wake up",
    answer: "okiru",
    display: "おきる",
  },
  {
    question: "to think",
    answer: "omou",
    display: "おもう",
  },
  {
    question: "to buy",
    answer: "kau",
    display: "かう",
  },
  {
    question: "to return",
    answer: "kaeru",
    display: "かえる",
  },
  {
    question: "to write",
    answer: "kaku",
    display: "かく",
  },
  {
    question: "to listen",
    answer: "kiku",
    display: "きく",
  },
  {
    question: "to come",
    answer: "kuru",
    display: "くる",
  },
  {
    question: "to know",
    answer: "shiru",
    display: "しる",
  },
  {
    question: "to do, to play",
    answer: "suru",
    display: "する",
  },
  {
    question: "to eat",
    answer: "taberu",
    display: "たべる",
  },
  {
    question: "to sleep",
    answer: "neru",
    display: "ねる",
  },
  {
    question: "to go out, to leave",
    answer: "deru",
    display: "でる",
  },
  {
    question: "to drink",
    answer: "nomu",
    display: "のむ",
  },
  {
    question: "to enter",
    answer: "hairu",
    display: "はいる",
  },
  {
    question: "to work",
    answer: "hataraku",
    display: "はたらく",
  },
  {
    question: "to speak",
    answer: "hanasu",
    display: "はなす",
  },
  {
    question: "to watch",
    answer: "miru",
    display: "みる",
  },
  {
    question: "to rest",
    answer: "yasumu",
    display: "やすむ",
  },
  {
    question: "to read",
    answer: "yomu",
    display: "よむ",
  },
  {
    question: "to understand",
    answer: "wakaru",
    display: "わかる",
  },
  {
    question: "to make",
    answer: "tsukuru",
    display: "つくる",
  },
  {
    question: "to wait",
    answer: "matsu",
    display: "まつ",
  },
  {
    question: "to teach",
    answer: "oshieru",
    display: "おしえる",
  },
  {
    question: "to live, to reside",
    answer: "sumu",
    display: "すむ",
  },
  {
    question: "to use",
    answer: "tsukau",
    display: "つかう",
  },
  {
    question: "to have, to hold",
    answer: "motsu",
    display: "もつ",
  },
  {
    question: "to open (something)",
    answer: "akeru",
    display: "あける",
  },
  {
    question: "to give",
    answer: "ageru",
    display: "あげる",
  },
  {
    question: "to put inside",
    answer: "ireru",
    display: "いれる",
  },
  {
    question: "to born",
    answer: "umareru",
    display: "うまれる",
  },
  {
    question: "to put, to place",
    answer: "oku",
    display: "おく",
  },
  {
    question: "to send",
    answer: "okuru",
    display: "おくる",
  },
  {
    question: "to memorize",
    answer: "oboeru",
    display: "おぼえる",
  },
  {
    question: "to swim",
    answer: "oyogu",
    display: "およぐ",
  },
  {
    question: "to get off, to get down",
    answer: "oriru",
    display: "おりる",
  },
  {
    question: "to lend",
    answer: "kasu",
    display: "かす",
  },
  {
    question: "to borrow",
    answer: "kariru",
    display: "かりる",
  },
  {
    question: "to think, to consider",
    answer: "kangaeru",
    display: "かんがえる",
  },
  {
    question: "to cut",
    answer: "kiru",
    display: "きる",
  },
  {
    question: "to wear",
    answer: "kiru",
    display: "きる",
  },
  {
    question: "to put out, to turn off",
    answer: "kesu",
    display: "けす",
  },
];

export default questions;
